[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "Why did he do so badly?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "he", "do", "so", "badly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "Well, you know, Piers, I don't think he did that badly.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "he", "did", "that", "badly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney", "Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "CC", "PRP", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "I think that we were all a little taken aback by Mitt Romney's performance and he --Mitt Romney had a great performance.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "we", "were", "all", "a", "little", "taken", "aback", "by", "Mitt", "Romney", "'s", "performance", "and", "he", "--", "Mitt", "Romney", "had", "a", "great", "performance", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "Sorry?", "question_tokens": ["Sorry", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "Is he right when he says that?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "right", "when", "he", "says", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 152, "question": "Do you believe him?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "Now if you do the math on that --", "answer_tokens": ["Now", "if", "you", "do", "the", "math", "on", "that", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$5 trillion"]}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "EX", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "WDT", "JJ", "$", "CD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "Do you believe him?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "-- there aren't enough loopholes and deductions that equal $5 trillion.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "there", "are", "n't", "enough", "loopholes", "and", "deductions", "that", "equal", "$", "5", "trillion", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "So he is lying, you think?", "question_tokens": ["So", "he", "is", "lying", ",", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "I don't think he's being honest about his tax cut.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "he", "'s", "being", "honest", "about", "his", "tax", "cut", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "So which is it?", "question_tokens": ["So", "which", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "Well, we shall find out, no doubt.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "shall", "find", "out", ",", "no", "doubt", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "Hey, Piers, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Hey", ",", "Piers", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "Stephanie Cutter wants an answer out of your guys.", "answer_tokens": ["Stephanie", "Cutter", "wants", "an", "answer", "out", "of", "your", "guys", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last week"], "PERSON": ["Stephanie", "Obama"]}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "Have you any idea?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "any", "idea", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "Well, first of all, I would say that listening to Stephanie's interview, I mean, it's just symptomatic of what's been going on with the Obama campaign since last week's debate.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "I", "would", "say", "that", "listening", "to", "Stephanie", "'s", "interview", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "it", "'s", "just", "symptomatic", "of", "what", "'s", "been", "going", "on", "with", "the", "Obama", "campaign", "since", "last", "week", "'s", "debate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "But do we anticipate from the Romney camp, from Mitt Romney himself, in the next 28 days, that we will get the devil of the detail on this?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "we", "anticipate", "from", "the", "Romney", "camp", ",", "from", "Mitt", "Romney", "himself", ",", "in", "the", "next", "28", "days", ",", "that", "we", "will", "get", "the", "devil", "of", "the", "detail", "on", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "Look, look, Piers, you know, President Obama has talked about reducing the corporate tax rate.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "look", ",", "Piers", ",", "you", "know", ",", "President", "Obama", "has", "talked", "about", "reducing", "the", "corporate", "tax", "rate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["next 28 days"], "PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 215, "question": "What are you anticipating?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "anticipating", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "Yes, sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "How have you dealt with the fallout from all this?", "question_tokens": ["How", "have", "you", "dealt", "with", "the", "fallout", "from", "all", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "Well, you know, people are going to have their own opinion, and that's the point.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "people", "are", "going", "to", "have", "their", "own", "opinion", ",", "and", "that", "'s", "the", "point", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "Why have you decided to change to Mitt Romney?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "have", "you", "decided", "to", "change", "to", "Mitt", "Romney", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "I would say because of the state of the country and I want the next four years to be different.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "say", "because", "of", "the", "state", "of", "the", "country", "and", "I", "want", "the", "next", "four", "years", "to", "be", "different", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "What do you think has been the predominant factor in the fury?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "has", "been", "the", "predominant", "factor", "in", "the", "fury", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "You know, in the -- I really don't understand the fury.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "in", "the", "--", "I", "really", "do", "n't", "understand", "the", "fury", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "Were you saddened?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "saddened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "I am.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "I mean, really disgusting.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "really", "disgusting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "You think it's stupid?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "it", "'s", "stupid", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "Just come on.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "come", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "Have you heard from Mitt Romney at all?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "heard", "from", "Mitt", "Romney", "at", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "Paul Ryan rang you today?", "question_tokens": ["Paul", "Ryan", "rang", "you", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "Yes, he did.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "he", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paul Ryan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "What did he say?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "he", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "He said thank you so much for your support and that I was brave and that they support me.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "said", "thank", "you", "so", "much", "for", "your", "support", "and", "that", "I", "was", "brave", "and", "that", "they", "support", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "Any of the Obama campaign been on?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "of", "the", "Obama", "campaign", "been", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "No, they haven't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "they", "have", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "What does it say to you about the state of the political discourse and debate in America that one innocuous tweet from you, purely because you're an actress and the color of your skin, sparked this kind of mayhem?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "it", "say", "to", "you", "about", "the", "state", "of", "the", "political", "discourse", "and", "debate", "in", "America", "that", "one", "innocuous", "tweet", "from", "you", ",", "purely", "because", "you", "'re", "an", "actress", "and", "the", "color", "of", "your", "skin", ",", "sparked", "this", "kind", "of", "mayhem", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "I think it tells me that our state -- the state of our country is that we are not united.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "tells", "me", "that", "our", "state", "--", "the", "state", "of", "our", "country", "is", "that", "we", "are", "not", "united", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama", "Obama"]}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", ":", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "So he's an Obama man?", "question_tokens": ["So", "he", "'s", "an", "Obama", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "He's an Obama -- yes, he's an Obama man and that's fine.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "an", "Obama", "--", "yes", ",", "he", "'s", "an", "Obama", "man", "and", "that", "'s", "fine", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "What do you make of it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "Well, I mean, listen, I think that it's unfortunate that anybody can make up their mind and vote however they want.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "listen", ",", "I", "think", "that", "it", "'s", "unfortunate", "that", "anybody", "can", "make", "up", "their", "mind", "and", "vote", "however", "they", "want", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "Do you think it was mainly because she was a black actress or because she was an actress and actually in Hollywood there aren't many actresses who say vote Mitt Romney?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "was", "mainly", "because", "she", "was", "a", "black", "actress", "or", "because", "she", "was", "an", "actress", "and", "actually", "in", "Hollywood", "there", "are", "n't", "many", "actresses", "who", "say", "vote", "Mitt", "Romney", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "EX", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "Well, I mean I think maybe there's some bit of both.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", "I", "think", "maybe", "there", "'s", "some", "bit", "of", "both", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Hollywood"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "So why the fury?", "question_tokens": ["So", "why", "the", "fury", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "I think there are lots of blacks supporting Romney.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "there", "are", "lots", "of", "blacks", "supporting", "Romney", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "Charles Blow?", "question_tokens": ["Charles", "Blow", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "Well, you can't say both things.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "ca", "n't", "say", "both", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charles"]}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "Rick, what do you make of what happened to him, to Jack Welch?", "question_tokens": ["Rick", ",", "what", "do", "you", "make", "of", "what", "happened", "to", "him", ",", "to", "Jack", "Welch", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "Well, again, you know, I think what we just heard from Charles, who is a prominent liberal, is exactly part of I think this problem, is that we whittle around the fact that when liberals are intolerant, we can't say it for some reason.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "again", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "think", "what", "we", "just", "heard", "from", "Charles", ",", "who", "is", "a", "prominent", "liberal", ",", "is", "exactly", "part", "of", "I", "think", "this", "problem", ",", "is", "that", "we", "whittle", "around", "the", "fact", "that", "when", "liberals", "are", "intolerant", ",", "we", "ca", "n't", "say", "it", "for", "some", "reason", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack Welch"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charles"]}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "Are you seriously saying that I didn't say that?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "seriously", "saying", "that", "I", "did", "n't", "say", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "What I'm saying, Charles, is that you can't just say that intolerance exists.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "I", "'m", "saying", ",", "Charles", ",", "is", "that", "you", "ca", "n't", "just", "say", "that", "intolerance", "exists", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "People are like we would vote for Clinton but why isn't the president doing this?", "question_tokens": ["People", "are", "like", "we", "would", "vote", "for", "Clinton", "but", "why", "is", "n't", "the", "president", "doing", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "I think that on the stump you get a much more passionate Barack Obama.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "on", "the", "stump", "you", "get", "a", "much", "more", "passionate", "Barack", "Obama", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Clinton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "How are you handling it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "handling", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "Well, it's the big white elephant in the room we can't avoid.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "the", "big", "white", "elephant", "in", "the", "room", "we", "ca", "n't", "avoid", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "Never.", "answer_tokens": ["Never", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 590, "question": "This is years old, right?", "question_tokens": ["This", "is", "years", "old", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NNS", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 591, "answer": "It's years.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 594, "question": "You didn't know you had been videotaped?", "question_tokens": ["You", "did", "n't", "know", "you", "had", "been", "videotaped", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 595, "answer": "No, I had no idea there was a camera set up.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "had", "no", "idea", "there", "was", "a", "camera", "set", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 596, "question": "Are you any nearer to knowing who betrayed you?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "any", "nearer", "to", "knowing", "who", "betrayed", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NN", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "At this point, no.", "answer_tokens": ["At", "this", "point", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "It was all about change.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "all", "about", "change", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 621, "question": "What do you make of America right now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "America", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 622, "answer": "I think we're in trouble.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "we", "'re", "in", "trouble", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "POS", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 631, "question": "When you go into bars and things, do people come up and try it on?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "go", "into", "bars", "and", "things", ",", "do", "people", "come", "up", "and", "try", "it", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "NNS", "VB", "RP", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 632, "answer": "No, that's what's so funny, is, you know, I really don't go to bars.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "that", "'s", "what", "'s", "so", "funny", ",", "is", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "really", "do", "n't", "go", "to", "bars", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121009pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 649, "question": "In terms of injuries you sustained, what physical shape are you in?", "question_tokens": ["In", "terms", "of", "injuries", "you", "sustained", ",", "what", "physical", "shape", "are", "you", "in", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "WP", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 650, "answer": "It's been a rough ride.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "been", "a", "rough", "ride", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]